-Mm, editorial coffee!
-Lovely.
Right!
The storming of capitol, how does it stand as news?
As news - pretty good.
It was very, very violent.
There was deadly violence, many injured themselves.
It was heavenly upset.
USA!
Then the question is: Was it unexpected?
The police did not seem to be prepared for so many to come.
The Capitoli Police had counted  m  ed a dissatisfaction demonstration.
instead it became a storm.
Then it was also so that if Trump tried to stay at the power-
-Then many people said in advance: "This is getting messy."
Sure, it's been talking about it for a long time.
But that's another thing-
-When the warnings for Trump's behavior become reality.
Thus, when a "parliamentary building" is stormed.
It is hard to see the pictures from the storm-
-Or to raise the eyebrows.
That is sick!
Then it is not in Sweden.
It is in the United States, on the other side of the Atlantic.
On the other hand, we seem to care a lot about what is happening in the United States.
But that may change in the future.
You don't know that.
That is the most important-
-This more than seeing it on TV, are things that happen in our everyday lives.
-But it does not end up on news sites, so it will not be news of it.
A bit like news is something you can make money from creating?
Absolutely!
One can make money on news-
-and "borrow the news clothes" to do it.
Journalism and news are something that we should confidence in.
Confidence you can try to earn without having earned it-
-Do to dress up their advertising so that it looks like journalism.
-There are fraudsters who work that way.
-In last election, 2016 ...
... when Hillary Clinton stood as a candidate against Donald Trump-
-It there a guy who created a fake yelling:
That she was involved in the murder of an FBI agent.
-Delete without being read.
That was the whole point to show:
"Lol! You are so departed, you who share articles without reading them."
Then there is the problem that headings do not keep what they promise.
You attract people on false grounds.
Clickbait and so on.
So basic, what we need is celebrities, a little action, a little drama.
-Do we have any good gossip?
-What so, big news ...
Then the principle of proximity applies, if it affects society ...
A celebrity?
"Moi!"
A second, only!
It would be good if we ...
Hi, Babes!
I have heard that educational radio, or ur-